LE YANG

Personal Information

Address: 12150 Ams Run, Carmel, Indiana 46032

PHONE: +1 718 7515228 емаіі: le.yang@gmail.com

Professional Summary

More than 13 years working with various information platforms, and 10 years working with the Allscripts Sunrise platform, including Clinical Manager, Emergency Care, eLink, SIM, and CDS; Core, interface, and customization team lead with major configuration and development experience; Implementation architect for workflow analysis and design, implementation, build, training, and activation support; Ability to create a safe and efficient patient care environment with process improvement and technology; Experience with business intelligence platforms and data analysis

CORE COMPETENCY

- · Project management
- Process review and improvement
- · Requirements gathering
- · Critical thinker
- Knowledge engineering
- Team leadership
- Compliance program development

- · Customer support and issue resolution
- Training development
- Clinical system implementation
- · Communication and interpersonal skills
- Perform well under pressure
- Attention to detail
- · Proven track record of project delivery results

KEY ACHIEVEMENTS

November 2018

Discharge Process Optimization

- Angular-based single page web app hosted in SCM. Centralized tool to facilitate patient discharge where previously providers were forced to use various non-connecting modules.
- Increase efficiency of discharging workflow related to consulting services, providers, nurses, and case managers.
- Increase usability and functionality of follow up appointment request and management.
- Improve quality and content of discharge instructions given to patient.
- Guide provider workflow aligned with hospital policies and regulatory requirements.

September 2018

Integration: Orchard Harvest Laboratory Information Systems

- Order and results interfaces between Harvest, Sunrise Clinical Manager, HCLL (blood bank), Quest (reference lab).
- ADT and financial interfaces between Harvest and Soarian Financials.

May 2018 | Integration: Soarian Financials

- Bi-directional ADT, scheduling, and financial interfaces between Soarian Financials and Sunrise Clinical Manager.
- Custom adapter to periodically query and generate batch charges.
- Automated charge reconciliation and error reporting.
- Update DRG and expected length of stay from interim coding.

March 2018

Microsoft Certified Solution Expert (MCSE): Data Management and Analytics Microsoft Certified Solutions Associate (MCSA): SQL 2016 Database Development

April 2017

CREST - Clinical Reasoning, Efficiency, and Surveillance Tools

- · University of Kentucky Medical Center's premier clinical decision support tools embedded into
- · A central dashboard for clinicians to review relevant and time-sensitive data in order to provide prompt clinical care to patients. Clinicians can perform various actions and interact with current chart directly from the dashboard.
- Improved clinical response efficiency by over 300% when compared to previous workflow.
- · Used modern web front- and back-end technology to deliver modular, fast, and aesthetically pleasing dashboard.
- · Leveraged platform API to provide tight integration and additional capabilities when used within enterprise EHR.

March 2017

SCM Web Service

- Designed and developed web service layered on top of SCM.
- · Provided end points for querying many clinical and business data e.g. visit, orders, documents, results, flowsheets, etc.
- Provided end point to add, delete, and update custom data.
- Allow rapid application development with easy data access and processing.
- Filled the critical missing piece in SCM product offering.

DECEMBER 2017

Automated JCode Waste Billing

- Respond to regulatory change to capture medication wastage, especially for high ticketed items.
- Automated waste charge entry from reported usage
- · Helped organization to reduce risk of losing many thousands of dollars in reimbursement due to potential missed wastage billing.

July 2016

Enterprise Data Batch Update

- Scheduled and on-demand batch update of clinical and business data.
- · Designed workflow to allow easy integration to update additional component. Initial release updates enterprise visit data and comment.
- Provided critical support to ER tracking.
- Replaced MLM-based approach that is error-prone and indeterministic.

June 2016

Continuous Integration

- Designed and setup automatic deployment and refresh of MLM upon code checking in.
- Enforced deployment workflow with syntax and status checking of committed assets.
- Improved accuracy and efficiency with new environment setup, such as during an upgrade.

February 2016

Medication Reconciliation Enhancements

- Automatic substitution of combo medication to component orders.
- Minimize order form open during admission reconciliation.
- Custom prompt for mandatory/required information without complete form open.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

07/2017 - 11/2018

Integration Consultant at Cumberland Consulting Group

Client: Jefferson Regional Medical Center, Arkansas

- HL7 Interface Engineer with Allscripts integration engine, eLink.
- Facilitated the planning of and execution of various integration initiatives to meet enterprise technical, security, and business requirements.
- Optimized integration and data flow strategy. Provided research data support to leadership in decision making process.
- Developed bi-directional interfaces to support data exchange between enterprise registration system (Soarian Financials), clinical system (Sunrise Clinical Manager), and various ancillary systems to support both standard messaging events and custom processes.
- Introduced documentation management system to client. Authored and maintained extensive technical documentation related to interface development and business processes.

03/2016-06/2017

MLM Writer & EHR Development (Independent Contractor)

Client: UK HealthCare, Kentucky

- Develop Medical Logic Modules (MLM's) using Arden Syntax standards to supplement system logic including alerts
 and hard stops, data integration, result processing, order generation, enforcement of adherence to workflows and automation of document or order entry.
- Plan, manage and lead the development, implementation, ongoing maintenance, testing, and support of the MLM enhancements to the enterprise clinical system.
- Monitor the system on a daily basis to ensure data integrity, consistency and accuracy.
- Work with other application team members to determine strategies for meeting service-specific needs through the implementation of MLM's.
- Integrate standard-based technologies within the Allscripts platform to deliver platform agnostic solutions to work orders and service requests.

04/2012-02/2016

Sr. Consultant at Leidos Health

10/2010-03/2012

Sr. Consultant at MMY Consulting Inc.

Client: St. Vincent Health, Indiana

- Developed custom tools and tabs leveraging Allscripts ObjectPlus platform. Executed full software development cycle
 from requirements gathering to testing to preparation of turn-over documentation including functionality overview,
 workflow diagrams, and technical references.
- Developed complex MLM's for clinical decision support, including many automated processes. Drafted architectural
 design guidelines for MLM development to improve coherence among direct and indirect execution of multiple MLM's
 to aid with process efficiency and to reduce failure points.
- Integrated ObjectPlus technologies with MLM development to deliver best user experience and process outcomes.
- Developed custom scripts to automate repetitive tasks: standard policy maintenance, charge maintenance, design point documents (formatting), test scripts (formatting).
- Developed custom queries for custom and ad hoc reporting, quality assurance, and feasibility analysis.
- Optimized stored procedures to improve query efficiency and accuracy.
- Lead projects to implement Sunrise platform to network hospitals to enable majority system function (CPOE, Pharmacy, Emergency Care, etc.) and to meet Meaningful Use requirements. Conducted future state analysis and addressed workflow gaps.
- Lead system upgrade projects. Performed impact analysis and lead design sessions, assisting end users with decisions on new functionality.
- Managed and supported system integration for Nutrition Services. Developed workflow recommendation and maintained related configuration items.
- Supported activation of various projects including big-bang CPOE rollout and system upgrades.
- Documented and categorized model system workflows, processes, and configured options.
- Conducted shared learning and knowledge sharing for team members.

07/2006-05/2009

Sr. Clinical Application Analyst

Bronx-Lebanon Hospital, New York City

- Participated in design, build and validation for system-wide Sunrise Clinical Manager EHR.
- Worked with and reported directly to C-level executives.
- Served as team lead for customization, core, and interfaces.
- Implemented all Allscripts Sunrise modules big bang in under 13 months, on time and on budget.

- Migrated and managed 20+ interfaces to new platform across multiple domains (ADT, results, document, financial, orders) while meeting previously established requirements.
- Established protocols for product documentation and change management.

TECHNICAL COMPETENCY

- Sunrise Clinical Manager (SCM)
- SCM 17.3 Training completed
- HL7 interface design and development (eLink)
- Business intelligence
- · Testing planning and execution
- Custom program development

- External data exchange
- Medical Logic Module (MLM) authoring
- · Scripting and task automation
- Data processing and transformation
- Structured content and presentation

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Expert: Arden, HL7, T-SQL

Intermediate: LaTeX, C#, XML/XSLT, JavaScript, TypeScript, Angular, web service (RESTful), reStructured-

Text, Python, WPF, VBA, HTML, Splunk, SSIS/SSRS, PowerShell

Basic: Shell Script, awk, sed

EDUCATION

June 2009 Baruch College, City University of New York, New York City

Master of Science in Finance

MAY 2007 Queens College, City University of New York, New York City

Bachelor of Arts in Computer Science

Minor in MATHEMATICS

CERTIFICATION

MARCH 2018 Microsoft Certified Solutions Expert (MCSE): Data Management and Analytics

Microsoft Certified Solutions Associate (MCSA): SQL 2016 Database Development